[{"question": "What is the coloured part of the human eye called?", "answers": ["Iris","Retina","Pupil","Cornea"]},
{"question": "Which of the following is a good conductor of electricity?", "answers": ["Salt","Rubber","Polymer","Plastic"]},
{"question": "What is the range of the pH scale?", "answers": ["0 to 14","0 to 15","10 to 20","0 to 9"]},
{"question": "Which organ is responsible for filtration?", "answers": ["Kidney","Liver","Lungs","Heart"]},
{"question": "What is the common name of Dihydrogen Monoxide?", "answers": ["Water","Carbon","Sulfate","Xenon"]},
{"question": "What is the first sense a baby develops?", "answers": ["Touch","Smell","Sight","Hearing"]},
{"question": "What kind of mammal is a platypus?", "answers": ["Montreme","Marsupial","Cetacean","Carnivore"]},
{"question": "What is the latin name for gold?", "answers": ["Aurum","Argentum","Cyprium","Stannum"]},
{"question": "What is etymology?", "answers": ["Study of word origin","Study of evolution","Study of cave formations","Study of weather patterns"]},
{"question": "What is the name of the outside part of the ear?", "answers": ["Auricle","Eardrum","Anvil","Cochlea"]},
{"question": "What does HDD mean in computer hardware/science?", "answers": ["Hard Disk Drive","Hard Drive Disk","Hard Drupal Drive","Hard Double Disk"]},
{"question": "Where is the thyroid gland?", "answers": ["Neck","Spine","Hip","Elbow"]},
{"question": "Where are the metatarsal bones?", "answers": ["Foot","Arms","Neck","Forearm"]},
{"question": "What organ produces bile?", "answers": ["Liver","Kidney","Lungs","Heart"]},
{"question": "How many stomachs do cows have?", "answers": ["4","5","6","3"]},
{"question": "How are the holes of swiss cheese made?", "answers": ["Carbon dioxide","Carbon monoxide","Sulfur Acetate","Acetic Acid"]},
{"question": "What is plastic made out of?", "answers": ["Oil","Carbon dioxide","Carbon Diphosphate","Silver"]},
{"question": "What is the only liquid metal?", "answers": ["Mercury","Titanium","Nickel","Iron"]},
{"question": "How can you calculate the age of a tree?", "answers": ["Ring count","Branch count","Leave count","Tree Height"]},
{"question": "What part of the heart suffers from a heart attack the most?", "answers": ["Myocardium","Aorta","Ventricles","Cardiac Vein"]},
{"question": "Which element is Ra in the periodic table?", "answers": ["Radium","Rhodium","Rubidium","Ruthenium"]},
{"question": "What is osmosis?", "answers": ["Diffusion of water molecules","Diffusion of carbon molecules","Diffusion of sulfur molecules","Diffusion of iron molecules"]},
{"question": "The Statue of Liberty is covered in what material?", "answers": ["Copper","Iron","Sulfur Acetate","Lead"]},
{"question": "What is lysergic acid commonly known as?", "answers": ["LSD","LCD","LDIO","LEAD"]},
{"question": "What is colostrum?", "answers": ["Milk produced by glands","Water produced by osmosis","Carbon emission from radiation","Half-life of iron"]},
{"question": "What is the speed of light?", "answers": ["2.998 x 10^8","2.998 x 10^13","6.024x10^23","9.89x10^9"]},
{"question": "What is the speed of sound?", "answers": ["343 m/s","329 m/s","299 m/s","3400 m/s"]},
{"question": "Whatis not an electrical SI unit for measurement?", "answers": ["Gallon","Dynamic Viscosity","Electric Charge","Electrical Field Strength"]},
{"question": "What animal skin is similar to ours?", "answers": ["Pig","Horse","Cow","Sheep"]},
{"question": "What are the building blocks of protein?", "answers": ["Amino Acids","Phosphoric Acid","Liquid Nitrogen","Electricity"]}
]
